Fabric and vinyl upholstery jobs!
Your trusted upholsterer 值得您信賴的室內裝潢家
picks up furniture from your house... 從您家取件
and delivers it back to you. 完工後直接送回您家
Get your estimate without obligation!
免費估價不強制購買！
Attention! 請注意！
Guaranteed results and great discounts!
免費估價不強制購買！
Attention!
請注意！
The upholsterer's truck 室內裝潢家已經來了！
has come to town!
Get your estimate without obligation!
免費估價不強制購買！
We upholster all types of furniture:
我們修整各種家具
chairs, three-seater sofas...
椅子，三人坐沙發...
OUT OF ORDER 真是太亂來了！
Paco! You too? Out partying?
Paco! 你也是？在外面玩瘋了嗎？
C'mon, mate!
大家一起來！
Mari Tere told me... Mari告訴我
she went to the pines 她到了海邊的松樹旁邊...
at the beach...
with Antonio and their little one,
和Antonio還有他們的小孩Jose。
José Manuel.
They saw a light in the distance 他們在遠處看到一個燈光，就過去看看那是什麼。
and went to see what it was.
As they got closer... 於是他們往那靠近
there was this smell of flowers 他們看到小花
長成強壯又大的花朵
that became stronger.
They got to the rocks 他們看到了松樹林中石頭
in the pine grove.
It was all lit up. 整個海灘突然被光充滿
They saw the figure 他們在光裡面看到
of the Virgin Mary in the light. 聖母瑪利亞的形象
Mari Tere says... Mari 說...
that the Virgin 聖母瑪利亞指了指JOSE
pointed at José Manuel.
She was like that for a while, 祂就這樣
then the lights disappeared. 指著Jose 好一陣子
She says that night... Mari說那天晚上
the Virgin got into her son's body.
聖母瑪利亞進到了JOSE的身體裡
And they've found out... 而且他們發現...
if you put your ear 如果你把耳朵貼在他的脖子後面
to the back of his neck,
you can hear the Virgin talk.
你就會聽到聖母瑪利亞說話
Don't threaten me! Don't!
不要威脅我！ 不要！
Don't you dare!
你敢！
How's things, Mari Carmen?
你好嘛？Carmen?
Getting by, Trini.
就過日子囉 Trini
Your turn to clean the stairs
this week? 你這禮拜輪到打掃樓梯阿
Yes. 是的
NUCLEUS 原子核
OUTER SPACE: 外太空:
STARS, PLANETS AND SPACESHIPS
星星，星球，和太空船
The mystery of the Virgin is 聖母瑪利亞神祕的地方是...很明顯祂總是用不同的方式出現
that she appears differently...
depending on who she talks to.
要看祂在跟誰說話
Me, I hear a young girl. 我聽到的是一個年輕女孩的聲音
Others hear an old lady. 有些人聽到老太太的聲音
She can speak in Valencian... 祂會說瓦倫西亞語（西班牙一種當地方言）
But she's always like a mother... 但祂永遠都像個母親
and you sort of feel safe, 好像你聽祂講話
listening to her. 就會有安心的感覺
She gives you kitchen recipes, 祂給你食譜
tips for the home, 持家妙方
she tells you 祂告訴你什麼商店在打折
what shops have discounts...
One day she told me:有一天，祂告訴我
40,099.
She just kept saying that. 祂只是一直重複這數字
So, I went to the newsagent's... 所以我去了書報攤
and saw that number there 然後我在樂透彩券上面看到了這組號碼
on a lottery ticket.
I bought it...我買了...
but I didn't win nothing at all. 不過什麼也沒得到...
He wouldn't let me see other guys!
他不讓我見其他男生！
He won't leave me alone!
他一直煩我！
He claims you had sex with him...
他說你有和他發生關係...
STAIRS CLEANIN SHIFT 樓梯清掃時間
MON, TUES, WED, FRI 週一 週二 週三
It's true! 是真的！
You shut up, liar! 你閉嘴你這騙子！
It's hot already. 嗯，已經熱了起來呢。
Too hot. 太熱了
Tomorrow's going to be even hotter. 明天還會更熱
And tomorrow's Saturday. 而且明天是禮拜六呢。
Trini!
Mum!媽！
Mari Carmen,
This letter is for José Vicente...
這封信給Mari的 Jose (脖子後面有聖母的)
and for my José Luis,
也給我的Jose
who cannot read.
他不識字
Don't try to find me 不用去找我
or worry about me. 也不用擔心我
It's hard to say good-bye. 說再見真的很難
But I'm really excited...
但一想到接下來會發生的事..
about what's going to happen to me.
我真的覺得好興奮
What lives inside Mari Tere's son...
住在Mari Tere的兒子身體裡面的
isn't the Virgin, 不是聖母瑪利亞
no matter what people say. 不管其他人怎麼說
It's someone from far away.
是一個從很遠的地方來的
And he told me...
而他告訴我...
that he can take me to his planet.
他可以帶我去他的星球。
A million miles from Earth.
離地球有一百萬哩
I had two dreams in life:
我這輩子就兩個夢想
having cats 養很多貓
and travelling into space. 還有在外太空旅行
The first one can't be 第一個無法實現
as I'm allergic. 因為我對貓過敏
As for my other dream, 至於我另一個夢想
this miracle's happened. 現在有奇蹟發生了
I'm really going to miss you.
我一定會想念你們的
I might see you from above.
我可能會從上面看著你
I'm not sure.
我不是很確定
But just in case, be good.
但為了以防萬一，要乖
I've left lots of food for you.
我留了很多食物給你
With all my love.
愛你們
MYSTERY